Jiaojiao,
are you willing to forgive me?
I'm not.
Jiaojiao,
I've caused you
and the family too much trouble.
I know I was wrong.
I used to think
you wanted to take over
for yourself.
But now I see
you've been doing it for the Su family.
I thought
I was capable of being the head.
But now I know
I don't deserve it.
I was wrong.
I'll change myself.
I'll listen to you
and you alone.
I won't complain.
Please forgive me.
Uncle,
although we always quarrel,
I've never hated you.
I'm sorry.
As long as you have the Su family in your heart,
we will always
be a family.
Zhen,
although the Escort Agency has suffered,
but the children
are finally united.
Father,
have you decided on the finale
for the royal speech contest?
It should be Cheng Qi
or Ling Feng.
Should?
Or?
Are you planning to tell the royals
like this in a few days?
I was set to marry Cheng Qi,
but my brother sent urgent messengers
to arrange for Ling Feng.
Where's the letter?
In that case,
let's do as Qijia said.
If we arrange for Ling Feng,
we might be questioned by the royal family.
Then find a way to get him through.
Do I need to teach you
do you need me to teach you?
Yes,
I'll take care of it right away.
Dad,
I've secured deals
with several major merchants in Yunjing.
Our business in the city
will be all ours from now on.
But don't get too excited just yet.
Colluding with bandits is a serious crime.
Zhang Xi Yun
wants to pin this charge on the Su family.
It's not foolproof.
If
Su Yuejiao comes out
and makes some trouble,
we may lose
the business.
Dad
Even if she doesn't go to jail,
just the suspicion of collusion with bandits,
her escort agency
can't run well in the future.
Your kick wasn't hard enough.
If you could have killed her on the spot,
the Su family
would be completely finished.
Don't worry, dad.
We'll have plenty of opportunities in the future.
Divorce with Su Yuejiao.
Be my guest.
I'm just an ordinary man
with little talent and knowledge.
I never thought I could be your confidant.
You said you were not talented.
Do you think the Yun State is without talent,
or the Starry Cloud Conference is a joke?
I thought you wanted to protect the Su's Escort Agency.
It's indeed
your arrangement.
I just made the arrangement.
But now,
the one who decides their fate
is you.
So if I divorce,
you'll
save the agency?
You seem
to have no leverage to negotiate with me.
If you don't want to marry me, that's fine.
But if you want to save the agency,
you must give up the title of Xingyun Champion.
and let Mr. Ling take it.
The title was
given by you.
If you want to take it back,
I have no objection.
Hold on.
I haven't finished.
Whether it's the poetry recital
or the poetry anthology,
as long as you write it,
people will think it's your work.
The literary world of the Yun State
will no longer have a place for Cheng Qi.
A nameless bumpkin like you,
do you even understand what elegance is?
Cheng Qi?
Never heard of him.
Probably some poor scholar from some remote village.
If I can win the competition and gain recognition,
I can change this trend.
I am the rule.
My book
[my books,]
[and make them accessible to all.]
[Let goodness take root,]
[and help our nation,]
[our literary circle,]
[prosper and thrive.]
[And let there be no more Cheng Qi.]
Of course,
a divorce is also necessary.
As long as you can move into this villa,
the Su family will
the Sus will be safe.
Ms. Zhang,
this is a big deal.
Can I have a few days to think about it?
Of course.
See?
I told you there would be delicious food.
You lost.
Grandpa,
this is the sweet cake and braised pork for you.
Jiao,
this is the pig's trotter soup I bought for you.
Drink it while it's hot.
What did Zhang Xi Yun want from you?
She didn't just ask you to bring food, did she?
The matter of the Escort Agency
should be resolved soon.
Really?
My brother-in-law,
you're really something.
I really underestimated you before.
Thanks.
Did you promise her something?
It was just a misunderstanding.
Once explained, it's all good.
Grandpa,
I have a favor to ask.
Your business is our business.
Go ahead.
Although we're still under lockdown,
the day after tomorrow
is the day for Jiao to take over.
I think it's not necessary to postpone it.
How about holding it as usual?
But now we can't get out.
What about the things needed for the ceremony?
You can leave the clothes to me.
Even if I don't sleep,
I can make it in time.
As for the incense table,
I've already prepared it.
It's not appropriate for you to do so.
It seems
I don't want My Lady to take over.
Well,
I have some new family emblems.
You can use them.
I...
Then I...
You can be in charge of the process.
It's okay to make the rest simple.
No.
It's a big deal for the Su family.
It can't be taken lightly.
Luckily, I was prepared.
It's in
the room for miscellaneous items.
Grandpa is so thoughtful.
Are you asleep?
No.
I can't sleep.
Is your wound hurting again?
No.
It's just that when I think about getting a handprint,
it seems unreal.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Gao Jiao
What are you going to do
after the handprint ceremony?
I'll take care of the Escort Agency.
I wasn't sure before.
But now I have you.
I feel at ease.
Silly.
The Escort Agency will be better and better.
It will be better and better.
Go to sleep.
No,
I have to find him.
Your master is fine.
He came out a few days ago
and even visited the Grand Preceptor's villa.
Do you know why he didn't tell me?
Why didn't he come to find me?
You never seem to care about me like this.
It's different.
Yeah.
I'm different
from your master.
You know I don't mean that.
Master.
Speak of the devil.
Miss Meng.
Can I borrow some money?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
My Lord.
Yicheng, come here.
This is all the money I have left.
Take it.
My Lord,
what do you mean?
I'm leaving the Escort Agency
and moving to the Prime Minister's garden.
If you want to stay in the Imperial City,
you can use the money
to propose to Miss Meng.
My Lord,
I have to follow you.
You can help me when you are outside.
Miss Meng is a good person.
She is a softie.
She won't treat you badly.
As for my father,
if he blames you,
just say I sold you out.
He won't make it hard for you.
My Lord,
you have more expenses than I do.
Have you made up your mind?
I've left the Escort Agency.
I'm willing to write for Mr. Ling.
Please let the Sus off the hook.
Do you care so much about Su Yuejiao?
Never mind.
I made the terms.
You're here.
I'll keep my promise.
But
if anything goes wrong at the speech contest,
I'll make sure to take care of your agency.
Take him away.
Look at his attitude.
Why not just let the government
punish the Sus?
I can use the Sus as long as he's on my side.
The speech contest is coming.
We should put the big picture first.
Besides,
I don't want a zombie in the future.
I don't understand
what's so good about Cheng Qi.
You've been so devoted to him.
He would sacrifice something
more important than his life for the one he loves.
How many men in the world can do that?
When he lives here for a long time,
he will
naturally treat me as his family,
cherish me,
and love me.
The food is getting cold.
Is my son-in-law coming back or not?
He must be drinking.
Where is
Qi?
He must be telling Tang Xin that he's safe.
Jiaojiao,
Qi is really considerate.
He knows to tell her that he's safe.
Unlike someone else,
who's so talkative.
You're the talkative one.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Finally, you're safe.
You were stuck in the escort agency.
I was so worried.
Did you run into any trouble?
Nothing at all.
Why aren't you eating?
Let's eat first.
Eat, eat, eat.
Where's Cheng Qi?
I don't know.
I haven't seen him since the end of the handprint.
It's really delicious.
I heard he went to the Prime Minister's villa recently.
He must have asked Ms. Zhang for help.
Maybe.
You guys eat first.
I'll be right back.
Who's there?
I'm Su Yuejiao.
I'd like to know
if my husband, Cheng Qi, is here.
Which Cheng Qi?
The top of the Starry Clouds Conference.
He's not here.
But your lady invited him here before.
No visitors today.
Just leave.
Cheng Qi,
where have you been?
She hasn't eaten anything today,
only drank alcohol.
She hasn't eaten anything else.
I see.
Keep serving her.
Don't miss any meal.
Yes, My Lady.
I didn't expect you to be so untrustworthy.
If you refuse to enter officialdom,
you'll never be the top poet.
You chose this.
To clear your agency's name,
you must be my man.
Otherwise, I can't ask my dad for help.
You chose this too.
To keep your talent from being wasted,
I let you write for me.
Yet you're always down.
No wonder your dad didn't like you.
You know everything about me.
I'm sure you know
that I always need some
beautiful girls,
singing and dancing,
or I can't
write anything good.
Do you do the same in the escort agency?
I'm afraid you've forgotten
that I used to write
in Huayue Tower.
So you want to listen to music?
You must have
plenty of musicians and dancers.
Or
do you have this hobby?
In that case,
I'll move the music house to your mansion.
What?
The Sus were released?
Yes.
It happened yesterday.
It's said that it's the Grand Preceptor's idea.
What the Grand Preceptor's idea?
It's Zhang Xi Yun's idea.
She must have received some benefits from the Sus.
This two-faced woman.
But she is the daughter of the Grand Preceptor.
We can't do anything to her.
She is untouchable.
But the Sus are not scary.
Yes.
By the way,
Have you arranged those people?
Yes.
They are all tight-lipped.
If they are caught as bandits,
they will say they are from Su's Escort Agency.
I have given them the money for the jail.
If they tell the truth,
their families...
We can't let the Su family rise again.
Pay attention to the escort in the city.
Don't let them take it back.
You can trust me.
Get out!
Guo Zheng, 21 years old,
is an official.
He's a good match for you.
Really? Thanks.
Meng Feifei.
Is Cheng Yicheng here?
What do you want from him?
Cheng Qi is missing.
I come here to take a chance.
He didn't go back to the agency.
He didn't get lost.
And he didn't tell you where he was going.
You should know where he might be.
I went there before.
They said he wasn't at the Grand Preceptor's Villa.
We'll know if we go and see.
Let's go.
I'm honored to perform for the royal family.
I can finally make my father proud.
Thank you for your help.
This cup of wine,
I toast to you.
Mr. Ling's talent is obvious to all,
and the speech for the royals will surely be well performed.
I have heard that
you are arranging a substitute writer for me.
May I ask
if you don't trust me?
It's all my brother's idea.
Don't get me wrong.
May I ask who will write the letter for me?
Isn't this the new Star King, Mr Cheng?
Ms Zhang.
You're so arrogant.
I can't believe you're working for someone.
Not at all.
I should thank Mr Ling for the opportunity.
And Ms Zhang for understanding me.
I came to this Star Conference
just hoping to have a chance
to enjoy myself in the capital.
Now I have both good wine and beautiful girls.
Why should I be the champion?
That's right.
Even if a chicken flies to the top of a tree,
it can't become a phoenix.
It's fine to make wild statements at the Xingyun Convention.
But if you act improperly
in the future...
Mr. Cheng,
you may be beheaded.
Exactly.
Instead of being so cautious,
why not
live in the moment?
Come, ladies,
let's dance another round.
He'll write the speech for you.
Don't worry, Mr. Ling.
That's true.
Thank you, Ms. Zhang.
You danced so well.
I'm glad you like it.
Let's go back and drink more.
Miss,
do you want to go with me?
Maybe another day.
I have a beauty
to keep me company today.
Cheng Qi,
do you know me?
Why don't you go home?
It's fun here.
This is my home.
Why are you here?
You left without a word that day.
The whole family is worried about you.
Why should I be worried?
You take care of your escort agency.
I'll write my book.
Writing a book?
Let Ling take the top spot on the Xingyun List.
and then write for him.
What happened?
Tell me!
Why so many questions?
This isn't a place for you. Leave.
We'll leave together.
Mr. Su,
this is the Grand Preceptor's villa,
not some wilderness.
You can't just come and go
as you please.
Miss Zhang,
I apologize for intruding
on your estate today.
Please allow me to take Cheng Qi away.
I will come to apologize another day.
Cheng Qi,
I thought you had made things clear with Mr. Su.
It's all in black and white.
I want a divorce.